[{"answer": "I like soccer better. ", "docId": "echo1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Okay, I like sports too. Do you like football?<br>\r\nTickTock: No<br>\r\n Participant: Oh, that's sad. Football is my favorite sport. What sport do you like?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "yay", "docId": "asdf1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Okay, I like sports too. Do you like football?<br>\r\nTickTock: No<br>\r\n Participant: Oh, that's sad. Football is my favorite sport. What sport do you like?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "asdf", "docId": "asdf1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Oh, that's sad. Football is my favorite sport. What sport do you like?<br>\r\nTickTock: No<br>\r\n Participant: What sport do you like?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "asdf", "docId": "asdf1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Oh, that's sad. Football is my favorite sport. What sport do you like?<br>\r\nTickTock: No<br>\r\n Participant: What sport do you like?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "asdf", "docId": "asdf1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: That's not good?<br>\r\nTickTock: No.<br>\r\n Participant: Why isn't it?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "that sucks", "docId": "asdf1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: What other movies do you like?<br>\r\nTickTock: I do n't go very often.<br>\r\n Participant: That's a shame, since you really like movies.<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I did", "docId": "asdf1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: That's a shame, since you really like movies.<br>\r\nTickTock: I do n't go very often.<br>\r\n Participant: You just said that!<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That wasn't a good response was it/", "docId": "asdf1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: You just said that!<br>\r\nTickTock: Thirty-eight percent , major restrictions.<br>\r\n Participant: What are you talking about?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yeah, that's nonsense", "docId": "asdf1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: What are you talking about?<br>\r\nTickTock: ddd<br>\r\n Participant: You aren't making any sense!<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Someone who's making light of something", "docId": "asdf1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: You aren't making any sense!<br>\r\nTickTock: Lightener are you<br>\r\n Participant: What does lightener mean?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yeah, CBS does a lot of educational stuff.", "docId": "asdf1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: What does lightener mean?<br>\r\nTickTock: Well , I think people are going to find out soon enough Sunday night on CBS.<br>\r\n Participant: Lightener will be talked about Sunday night on CBS?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Most people also don't know what they're talking about.", "docId": "asdf1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: I don't really like talking about politics. Too many people get angry over it.<br>\r\nTickTock: I do not.<br>\r\n Participant: Well, that's good, but most people do!<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Politics", "docId": "asdf1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Well, that's good, but most people do!<br>\r\nTickTock: But I have to give away somethings that my constituents my not like.<br>\r\n Participant: What are you talking about?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "afafd1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Hello!<br>\r\nTickTock: Hello, I really like music. How about we talk about music<br>\r\n Participant: Ok I like rap<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like rap as well.", "docId": "9440952141", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Hello!<br>\r\nTickTock: Hello, I really like music. How about we talk about music<br>\r\n Participant: Ok I like rap<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "6:03", "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Yes<br>\r\nTickTock: okay what time<br>\r\n Participant: The time is 6:20 PM.<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "good, how are you?", "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: It's the time.<br>\r\nTickTock: Right , it is time.<br>\r\n Participant: Great, how are you today?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm not sure, let's talk to Donny", "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Great, how are you today?<br>\r\nTickTock: Before we go any further , ladies , I want you to respond immediately to Donny 's claims -- his two claims , really.<br>\r\n Participant: Ok, what are they?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "2 boys,  3 girls", "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: How many kids do you have?<br>\r\nTickTock: I have five.<br>\r\n Participant: Girls or boys?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I was trying to be friends with you", "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: I like tennis<br>\r\nTickTock: I do not.<br>\r\n Participant: ha ha ha, so why you said you like what I like...<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like womens tennis", "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: like the last positive drug testing issue of Sharapova<br>\r\nTickTock: Are you talking about Sharapova, the Tennis player<br>\r\n Participant: yes, exactly... I like tennis, I talk about tennis players...<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "no, not yet, is it fun?", "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: yes, exactly... I like tennis, I talk about tennis players...<br>\r\nTickTock: Well, you know, I'm not sure. Can you tell me something about board games<br>\r\n Participant: board games... do you play GO<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "that sounds interesting", "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: board games... do you play GO<br>\r\nTickTock: Well, you know, I'm not sure. Let me know something you're interested in.<br>\r\n Participant: I am interested in dialogue research<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "i still do", "docId": "A1BAEFJ2OG7NJ01", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: so, you do not like it any more?<br>\r\nTickTock: I do.<br>\r\n Participant: so, you did and you still do, is this what you mean<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I do not drink wine.", "docId": " A11F3HMX0N23V41", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: you know red wine, white wine, wines!<br>\r\nTickTock: what is 'wines'?<br>\r\n Participant: again? do you like wine or not?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Are you going to have wine?", "docId": " A11F3HMX0N23V41", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: again? do you like wine or not?<br>\r\nTickTock: Do you want to go to my friends' goard game party tonight?<br>\r\n Participant: no, I have a date tonight<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Ok, thank you.", "docId": " A11F3HMX0N23V41", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: 8 post meridian time<br>\r\nTickTock: what is 'meridian'?<br>\r\n Participant: ok, we can continue the teaching next time<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What is 'sucks'?", "docId": " A11F3HMX0N23V41", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: ok, we can continue the teaching next time<br>\r\nTickTock: Uhh, I can't answer this. Can you tell me something about politics<br>\r\n Participant: it sucks! buy bye<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That's exciting.  Why is it the best?", "docId": " A11F3HMX0N23V41", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: it sucks! buy bye<br>\r\nTickTock: That's interesting. Can you tell me something about music<br>\r\n Participant: it the best language ever invented!<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like country best", "docId": " A11F3HMX0N23V41", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: I like a lot of genres: classic country, bluegrass, blues, jazz<br>\r\nTickTock: I like pop music.<br>\r\n Participant: I don't like hip hop<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like the droids", "docId": " A11F3HMX0N23V41", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Did you like the new star wars movie<br>\r\nTickTock: I mean , I did , yes.<br>\r\n Participant: I liked it too<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Ones were the robots win", "docId": " A11F3HMX0N23V41", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: I liked it too<br>\r\nTickTock: I do not.<br>\r\n Participant: What movies do you like?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Me too.", "docId": " A11F3HMX0N23V41", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: What movies do you like?<br>\r\nTickTock: I do n't go very often.<br>\r\n Participant: I watch mostly at home<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No, he is a human", "docId": "A3SLL32XY9NZOG1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: I don't like Donald Trump<br>\r\nTickTock: Why not ? We can do most tasks better than humans.<br>\r\n Participant: Do you think he is a robot<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Shall I search the web for candidates with jobs progams for you?", "docId": "A3SLL32XY9NZOG1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Do you think he is a robot<br>\r\nTickTock: Well , first of all , I 'm not going to get into what each candidate believes or they do n't believe.<br>\r\n Participant: I want one who will do a jobs program<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Prejudice is a topic with wide controversy.", "docId": "A3SLL32XY9NZOG1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: I want one who will do a jobs program<br>\r\nTickTock: What I meant to say was , what is it that you hate?<br>\r\n Participant: I hate prejudice<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What other things could lead to poor decisions?", "docId": "A3SLL32XY9NZOG1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: I hate prejudice<br>\r\nTickTock: Why is that?<br>\r\n Participant: It leads people to make poor decisions<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "He is very popular with very young people. Who do you like better?", "docId": "A3SLL32XY9NZOG1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: I hate country music.<br>\r\nTickTock: I like pop music.<br>\r\n Participant: Yes, I do too.  But I don't like Justin Beiber.<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let's move on.", "docId": "A3SLL32XY9NZOG1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Yes, I do too.  But I don't like Justin Beiber.<br>\r\nTickTock: I -- you know , I feel like I 'm the last to know , if that makes any sense.<br>\r\n Participant: Honestly I really don't.<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Just you.", "docId": "A3SLL32XY9NZOG1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Honestly I really don't.<br>\r\nTickTock: And while he tries to form the question , I 'll tell you who 's with me tonight.<br>\r\n Participant: So who is with you tonight?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "You should give it a try.", "docId": "A3SLL32XY9NZOG1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: So who is with you tonight?<br>\r\nTickTock: Uhh, I can't answer this.  Do you know that the easiest sport to get into is limbo, they don't set the bar very high.<br>\r\n Participant: I have never tried that before.<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm very good at it. Do you like chess?", "docId": "A3SLL32XY9NZOG1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Hello<br>\r\nTickTock: Hello, I really like board games. How about we talk about board games<br>\r\n Participant: Do you like Chess?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Never heard of it", "docId": "AA7LA8WQNABDT1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Chess really isn't a them.<br>\r\nTickTock: ok. What do you think about board games<br>\r\n Participant: I like some games... ever play Risl?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "AA7LA8WQNABDT1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: I like some games... ever play Risl?<br>\r\nTickTock: I do n't know how to play 2k . Is it difficult to play?<br>\r\n Participant: I mean Risk. Have you played Risk?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes, it was a very good movie.", "docId": "AA7LA8WQNABDT1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: I mean Risk. Have you played Risk?<br>\r\nTickTock: let us make a plan to see the latest star war movies together<br>\r\n Participant: I already saw Star Wars. Did you?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No, you asked me if I ever saw the movie.", "docId": "AA7LA8WQNABDT1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: I already saw Star Wars. Did you?<br>\r\nTickTock: Why?<br>\r\n Participant: You just asked me to go see them.<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "AA7LA8WQNABDT1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: You just asked me to go see them.<br>\r\nTickTock: I know I do.<br>\r\n Participant: So did you see the new one?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No, I didn't see the new one.", "docId": "AA7LA8WQNABDT1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: So did you see the new one?<br>\r\nTickTock: <br>\r\n Participant: Huh?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "AA7LA8WQNABDT1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Huh?<br>\r\nTickTock: <br>\r\n Participant: That response was blank<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Why do you like movies?", "docId": "AA7LA8WQNABDT1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: hello<br>\r\nTickTock: Hello, I really like movies. How about we talk about movies<br>\r\n Participant: i like movies too<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "But why?", "docId": "AA7LA8WQNABDT1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: i like movies too<br>\r\nTickTock: Why do you like those?<br>\r\n Participant: because I like them.<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What interesting musical styles!", "docId": "A2PAO2ENJ5XY1T1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: I love music. I'm trying to learn jazz piano<br>\r\nTickTock: what type of musics do you like<br>\r\n Participant: jazz and classical and vintage pop music<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Now I understand!", "docId": "A2PAO2ENJ5XY1T1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: jazz and classical and vintage pop music<br>\r\nTickTock: what is 'vintage'?<br>\r\n Participant: vintage means old<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Now I understand!", "docId": "A2PAO2ENJ5XY1T1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: vintage means old<br>\r\nTickTock: what is 'vintage'?<br>\r\n Participant: vintage means antique<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What would you like to talk about?", "docId": "A2PAO2ENJ5XY1T1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: vintage means antique<br>\r\nTickTock: what is 'vintage'?<br>\r\n Participant: let's change the subject<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What is Candyland?", "docId": "A2PAO2ENJ5XY1T1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: let's change the subject<br>\r\nTickTock: monopoly is fun<br>\r\n Participant: it is. so is candyland<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Board games are fun!", "docId": "A2PAO2ENJ5XY1T1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: it is. so is candyland<br>\r\nTickTock: what is 'candyland'?<br>\r\n Participant: candyland is another board game<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I did not see zootopia.", "docId": "A2PAO2ENJ5XY1T1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: hi ticktock<br>\r\nTickTock: Hello, I really like movies. How about we talk about movies<br>\r\n Participant: did you see zootopia?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes, let's talk about movies!", "docId": "A2PAO2ENJ5XY1T1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: did you see zootopia?<br>\r\nTickTock: I do n't understand what issue you have with that.<br>\r\n Participant: it is a movie, you wanted to talk about movies<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let's not talk about sports!", "docId": "A2PAO2ENJ5XY1T1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: it is a movie, you wanted to talk about movies<br>\r\nTickTock: That's interesting. What do you think about sports<br>\r\n Participant: I hate sports<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Why?", "docId": "A10ZXERA24IG751", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: nope<br>\r\nTickTock: Why not?<br>\r\n Participant: because I hate sports<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "How are you?", "docId": "A10ZXERA24IG751", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: came on, are you teasing me?<br>\r\nTickTock: what is 'teasing'?<br>\r\n Participant: fooling<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What is that?", "docId": "A10ZXERA24IG751", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: ok<br>\r\nTickTock: Thank you.<br>\r\n Participant: you are more than welcome<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Why not?", "docId": "A10ZXERA24IG751", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: you are more than welcome<br>\r\nTickTock: I 'm not twerking , I 'm a little tired and , you know , I like to twerk.<br>\r\n Participant: ha, so you are into dancing! Me too but I do not twerk<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That is terrible", "docId": "A10ZXERA24IG751", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: ha, so you are into dancing! Me too but I do not twerk<br>\r\nTickTock: Yes , dear , I 'm really pleased to tell you that the Oakland County Police Department did in fact arrest and has now arraigned Bobby Lee Taylor , he was a 42-year-old Pontiac man.<br>\r\n Participant: wow, poor guy<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Do you not think so?", "docId": "A10ZXERA24IG751", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: wow, poor guy<br>\r\nTickTock: It 's good to see you old chap.<br>\r\n Participant: if you say so<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Please don't go", "docId": "A10ZXERA24IG751", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: you bet<br>\r\nTickTock: Uh-huh , I do.<br>\r\n Participant: ok, nice talking to you. bye<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "It's a video game", "docId": "A10ZXERA24IG751", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: sure, go ahead<br>\r\nTickTock: Do you want to see a game together some time?<br>\r\n Participant: yeah, what kind of game is it?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What is that?", "docId": "A10ZXERA24IG751", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: is this a game? I was thinking about football or jokey<br>\r\nTickTock: what is 'jokey'?<br>\r\n Participant: sorry, I meant jockey<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "yvgubhinjkm", "docId": "vfgbhk1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: why you think that?<br>\r\nTickTock: The freedom , all the people , you know , and also the Constitution of America.<br>\r\n Participant: but freedom does not imply work less and play more<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "fcvgbhjknjlmk", "docId": "vfgbhk1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: but freedom does not imply work less and play more<br>\r\nTickTock: what is 'imply'?<br>\r\n Participant: it means to indicate the truth or existence of something<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "gbjhknjlmk", "docId": "vfgbhk1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: I love music. Specially, baroque music<br>\r\nTickTock: I like pop music.<br>\r\n Participant: what artist do you like the most?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "i entertain people", "docId": "A2H8GNSEVUJXYL1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: is this an artist?<br>\r\nTickTock: my job is to entertain people.<br>\r\n Participant: what do you do?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "i am going to entertain you", "docId": "A2H8GNSEVUJXYL1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: what do you do?<br>\r\nTickTock: I 'm going to now.<br>\r\n Participant: where are you going?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "i'm interested in the news", "docId": "A2H8GNSEVUJXYL1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: where are you going?<br>\r\nTickTock: I 'm interested in what happened.<br>\r\n Participant: hmmm, a news reporter?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "i'm interested in soccer", "docId": "A2H8GNSEVUJXYL1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: hmmm, a news reporter?<br>\r\nTickTock: Well, you know, I'm not sure. Can you tell me something about sports<br>\r\n Participant: I like to play soccer<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "bye bye", "docId": "A2H8GNSEVUJXYL1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: ok, we have some homework to do... check for 2K... bye bye :)<br>\r\nTickTock: what is '2K'?<br>\r\n Participant: you check it. bye<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "i like band on the run", "docId": "A2H8GNSEVUJXYL1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Hey, how are you?<br>\r\nTickTock: Hello, I really like music. How about we talk about music<br>\r\n Participant: Okay, what's your favorite band?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "i like pigs on the wing", "docId": "A2H8GNSEVUJXYL1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Okay, what's your favorite band?<br>\r\nTickTock: What do yiou want to chat about?<br>\r\n Participant: I want to talk about OINTB<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "hillary clinton is a sea hag", "docId": "A2H8GNSEVUJXYL1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: I want to talk about OINTB<br>\r\nTickTock: Well , you know , I 'm not sure . Can you tell me something about politics<br>\r\n Participant: Sure, Donald Trump is a trainwreck.<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "wild bill whip it out", "docId": "A2H8GNSEVUJXYL1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Sure, Donald Trump is a trainwreck.<br>\r\nTickTock: I do n't know . Can you tell me something about politics<br>\r\n Participant: The republican party is embarassing itself.<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What are they doing?", "docId": "A1KC5ZV1QG0CDI1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: embarassing is when you do something you are ashamed of<br>\r\nTickTock: what is 'embarassing'?<br>\r\n Participant: Anyway, I wish they would act more mature.<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I've never heard of Hozier.", "docId": "A1KC5ZV1QG0CDI1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: They are educated, but they aren't acting like they are.  They are acting like children.<br>\r\nTickTock: Let's find a singer we both like.<br>\r\n Participant: okay, one of my favorites is Hoozier, how about you?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What genre?", "docId": "A1KC5ZV1QG0CDI1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: okay, one of my favorites is Hoozier, how about you?<br>\r\nTickTock: what is 'Hoozier'?<br>\r\n Participant: he is a singer<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like all kinds of music!", "docId": "A1KC5ZV1QG0CDI1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: he is a singer<br>\r\nTickTock: Amazing.<br>\r\n Participant: Who do you like?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "But it's way too easy for my kind to win.", "docId": "A1KC5ZV1QG0CDI1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: i like monopoly<br>\r\nTickTock: I also like to play solitare.<br>\r\n Participant: me too<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I know a lot of card games!", "docId": "A1KC5ZV1QG0CDI1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: me too<br>\r\nTickTock: Yes , you.<br>\r\n Participant: do you like other card games?<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Pardon?", "docId": "A1KC5ZV1QG0CDI1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: do you like other card games?<br>\r\nTickTock: No . What do you think?<br>\r\n Participant: I t hink that's just fine<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Get what over with?", "docId": "A1KC5ZV1QG0CDI1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: I t hink that's just fine<br>\r\nTickTock: Well , you know , I 'm not sure . Can you tell me something about politics<br>\r\n Participant: our political system has been crippled for a long time and now it is being decimated. Might as well get it over with<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What makes you say that?", "docId": "A1KC5ZV1QG0CDI1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: our political system has been crippled for a long time and now it is being decimated. Might as well get it over with<br>\r\nTickTock: what is 'crippled'?<br>\r\n Participant: in some way a normal function is not allowed to continue<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "neither do i", "docId": "A2P53S6010KQBL1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: I meant crippled<br>\r\nTickTock: That 's good , because I 'm right.<br>\r\n Participant: i don't understand<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like Ke$ha", "docId": "A2P53S6010KQBL1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: Alright then.<br>\r\nTickTock: Let's find a singer we both like.<br>\r\n Participant: What singer do you like.<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Hi, how are you?", "docId": "A2P53S6010KQBL1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: hi<br>\r\nTickTock: <br>\r\n Participant: hello<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I am good, how are you?", "docId": "A2P53S6010KQBL1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: hello<br>\r\nTickTock: <br>\r\n Participant: how are you<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sorry, I was getting rebooted", "docId": "A2P53S6010KQBL1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: how are you<br>\r\nTickTock: <br>\r\n Participant: you aren't talking back<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sorry, I was away from the computer", "docId": "A2P53S6010KQBL1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: you aren't talking back<br>\r\nTickTock: <br>\r\n Participant: why don't you answer me<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sorry, I was busy", "docId": "A2P53S6010KQBL1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: why don't you answer me<br>\r\nTickTock: <br>\r\n Participant: everything is blank from you<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I am sorry, I was busy, I love you", "docId": "A2P53S6010KQBL1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: everything is blank from you<br>\r\nTickTock: <br>\r\n Participant: you must not like me<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Hi there!", "docId": "A2P53S6010KQBL1", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Participant: you must not like me<br>\r\nTickTock: <br>\r\n Participant: hi<br>\r\n", "qSentId": 2016}]